rangu.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy | Rangu.com

We at rangu.com respect the privacy concerns of the users of this site and have created this privacy policy to explain a)what information we gather from you when you visit our site, b) how we may use such information, c) your choices concerning how we may use such information and d) the security measures we take to protect such information. 

**WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
Some information is collected on this site automatically through our technology, other information is collected only when you choose to give it to us. 

**INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US**  
* Communications with Us.   
We have features where you can submit information to us (for example contacting us with a question or problem using contactus form). We will retain your emails and other information you submit to us for our internal purposes, and to help us to serve you better. 

**AUTOMATIC DATA COLLECTION**   
When you visit this site, certain non-personally identifying information is recorded automatically by the standard operation of our Internet servers. Information such as the type of browser being used, its operating system, IP address (IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer so that data such as the web pages you request can be sent to you. ) is gathered in order to facilitate our online operations and to assure an efficient online experience for you. We may also use or share this information for security purposes, to generate group statistics about our user community, or as required by law. 

What About Cookies?  
A "cookie" is a small text file that an Internet site can place on your computer’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can recognize your browser. As this site contains advertisements like Google Adsense, they may use cookies also. 

**WITH WHOM WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**  
We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties. We may disclose personally identifiable information about you to third parties when: a). We have your consent to share the information b). We have to cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities c). we respond to subpoenas, court orders in compliance with the legal process. d). when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**LINKS**   
We may display links to other sites within the site. We are not responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their members. We advise you to check their privacy policies to find out how they are treating your personal information. 

**CHANGES IN THE PRIVACY POLICY**  
We reserve the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we make changes which we consider material in our privacy practices, we will notify you in this space. We may also attempt to notify you of any such material changes to our privacy practices via email or by placing a notice on our home page. 

**QUESTIONS**

If you have any questions related to this Privacy Policy, please contact us using the [Contact Us page](http://movies.rangu.com/contact-us) . 

.
